{
    "subject": "Harold_Nicholas",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Dorothy_Dandridge",
    "human_readable": "Harold Nicholas is married to Dorothy Dandridge.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.925239086151123,
            "question": "Is Harold Nicholas married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195151329040527,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Harold Nicholas and Dorothy Dandridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9116685390472412,
            "question": "To whom was Harold Nicholas married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9115318655967712,
            "question": "Who is married to Dorothy Dandridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.908630907535553,
            "question": "Who are Harold Nicholas and Dorothy Dandridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9067540764808655,
            "question": "Is Dorothy Dandridge married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8607615232467651,
            "question": "Name a famous actress married to Harold Nicholas."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7513518333435059,
            "question": "Who is Harold Nicholas?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6956045627593994,
            "question": "What was the name of Dorothy Dandridge's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.680593729019165,
            "question": "What is the name of Dorothy Dandridge's husband?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Harold Nicholas is married to Dorothy Dandridge.",
            "html": "yago_6117_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Dorothy Dandridge's husband?",
            "html": "yago_6117_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Harold Nicholas?",
            "html": "yago_6117_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a famous actress married to Harold Nicholas.",
            "html": "yago_6117_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6117_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Harold Nicholas was married to Dorothy Dandridge."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Harold Nicholas was married to Dorothy Dandridge, with varying details on their marriage dates and duration."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}